Guide to the Poly Archives Serial Publications Collection RG.030
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XIV: Polytechnic News, 11809
  The Polytechnic News bulletin underwent slight title and audience changes over the years, but remained a widely distributed source of information about faculty research and happenings around Polytechnic. From 1955-1956 the bulletins were titled "Report from Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn." In 1957, the headline changed to "News from Polytechnic: A newsletter for the faculty in staff." In 1970, this title was tweaked to "The Polytechnic Faculty News: For faculty and staff of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn." In 1974, the title changed to "Polytechnic News: A Newsletter of Polytechnic Institute of New York," which indicated both the university's name change and, no longer specifying faculty as the only audience, a wider distribution. In 1984 the title became "Poly News: Polytechnic Institute of New York - Newsletter - Brooklyn - Long island - Westchester." Finally, in 1986, reflecting yet another name change to the university, the title changed to "Poly News: Polytechnic University - Newsletter - Brooklyn - Long island - Westchester."
  The series is arranged chronologically, with all name variations grouped together under the general series title "Polytechnic News." Bound volumes follow loose issues in boxes and folders.
  - Report from the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, Volume 1, No. 1-5, 1955-1956; 12022 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Report from the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, Volume 2, No. 1-2, 1956; 12023 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - News from Polytechnic, Volume 1, No. 1-4, 1957; 12024 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - News from Polytechnic, Volume 2, No. 1-3, 1958-1959; 12025 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - News from Polytechnic, Volume 3, No. 1, 1959; 12026 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - News from Polytechnic, November 1960 - March 1961, 1960-1961; 12027 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - News from Polytechnic, April 1961 - September 1961, 12028 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - News from Polytechnic, October 1961 - February 1963, 1961-1963; 12029 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - News from Polytechnic, May 1963 - July 1964, 1963-1964; 12030 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - News from Polytechnic, Index 1955 - 1964, undated; 12031 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 6, No. 51-56, 1970 June - September; 12181 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 7, No. 1-13, 1970 September - November; 12182 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 7, No. 15-27, 1970-1971; 12183 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 7, No. 28-38, 1971 February - April; 12184 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 7, No. 40-53, 1971 May - August; 12185 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 8, No. 2-18, 1971 September - December; 12186 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 8, No. 19-48, 1972 January - September; 12187 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News, Volume 9, No. 1-14, 19, 36, 57, 1972-1973; 12188 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 10, No. 48, 1974 May; 12189 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 11, No. 18-51, 1975 January - August; 12190 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 12, No. 1-59, 1975-1976; 12191 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 13, No. 1-30, 1976-1977; 12192 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 14, No. 14, 1978 July; 12193 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 15, No. 1-27, 1978-1979; 12194 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 16, No. 1-12, 1979-1980; 12195 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 16, No. 13-24, 1980 March - August; 12196 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 17, No. 1-23, 1980-1981; 12197 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 18, No. 1-8, 1981 September - December; 12198 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 18, No. 9-25, 1982 January - August; 12199 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 19, No. 1-20, 1982-1983; 12200 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 20, No. 1-8, 1983 September - December; 12201 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Polytechnic News, Volume 21, No. 1-9, 1984 January - November; 12202 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Poly News, Volume 22, No. 1-3, 1985 January - March/April; 12203 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Poly News, Volume 22, No. 4-7, 1985 Aummer - November/December; 12204 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Poly News, Volume 23, No. 1-4, 1986 January/February - Winter; 12205 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Poly News, Volume 24, No. 1-4, 1987 Spring - Winter; 12206 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Poly News, Volume 22, No. 1-2, 1988 Spring/Summer - Fall; 12207 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Poly News, Volume 23, No. 1-3, 1989 Winter - Fall; 12208 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Poly News, Volume 24, No. 1-2, 1990 Spring - Fall; 12209 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Poly News, Volume 25, No. 1, 1991 Fall; 12210 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Poly News, Volume 26, No. 1, 1992 Winter; 12211 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Polytechnic News Volume XIII (bound), 1976-1977; 12212 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Polytechnic News Volume XIV (bound), 1977-1978; 12213 (Box 10, Item 2)
  - Polytechnic News Volume XV (bound), 1978-1979; 12214 (Box 10, Item 3)
  - Polytechnic News Volume XVI (bound), 1979-1980; 12215 (Box 10, Item 4)
  - Polytechnic News Volume XVII (bound), 1980-1981; 12216 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - Polytechnic News Volume 12 - 14 (binder), 1975-1978; 12217 (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Polytechnic News Volume 15 - 17 (binder), 1978-1981; 12218 (Box 10, Item 7)
  - Polytechnic News Volume 18 - 21 (binder), 1981-1984; 12219 (Box 10, Item 8)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume I (bound), 1964-1965; 12264 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 1)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume II (bound), 1965-1966; 12265 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 2)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume III (bound), 1966-1967; 12266 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 3)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume IV (bound), 1967-1968; 12267 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 4)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume V (bound), 1968-1969; 12268 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 5)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume VI (bound), 1969-1970; 12269 (Item Shelf 36/4F, Item 6)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume VII (bound), 1970-1971; 12270 (Item Shelf 36/5F, Item 7)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume VIII (bound), 1971-1972; 12271 (Item Shelf 36/5F, Item 8)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume IX (bound), 1972-1973; 12272 (Item Shelf 36/5F, Item 9)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume X (bound), 1973-1974; 12273 (Item Shelf 36/5F, Item 10)
  - Polytechnic Faculty News Volume XI (bound), 1974-1975; 12274 (Item Shelf 36/5F, Item 11)
- Series XV: Polytechnite, 11841
  Polytechnic was the student newspaper for the evening students of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn.
  - Polytechnite 1949-1950, 12539 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Polytechnite 1953, 12540 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Polytechnite 1954, 12541 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Polytechnite 1955, 12542 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Polytechnite 1956, 12543 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Polytechnite 1957, 12544 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Polytechnite 1958, 12545 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Polytechnite 1958-1959, 12546 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Polytechnite 1959, 12547 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Volume 1, 1941-1942; 12276 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Item 1)
  - Volume 2, 1942-1943; 12277 (Item Shelf 36/6F, Item 2)
  - Volume 3, 1943-1944; 12278 (Item Shelf 36/6F, Item 3)
  - Volume 4, 1944-1945; 12279 (Item Shelf 36/6F, Item 4)
  - Index 1941 - 1944, undated; 12280 (Item Shelf 36/6F, Item 5)
- Series XVI: Polywog, Innovations, and Legacy, 11842
  Polywog was Polytechnic's yearbook for the Brooklyn campus (1887 - 2009). Innovations (1986-1993) and Legacy (1994-2002) were yearbooks published by Polytechnic's Long Island campus.
  - Polywog Index to 1889, 1971; 12548 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Polywog Index to 1898, 12549 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Polywog 1887, 12284 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 1)
  - Polywog 1888, 12285 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 2)
  - Polywog 1889, 12286 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 3)
  - Polywog 1890, 12287 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 4)
  - Polywog 1899, 12288 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 5)
  - Polywog 1900, 12289 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 6)
  - Polywog 1901, 12290 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 7)
  - Polywog 1902, 12291 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 8)
  - Polywog 1903, 12292 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 9)
  - Polywog 1904, 12293 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 10)
  - Polywog 1905, 12294 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 11)
  - Polywog 1906, 12295 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 12)
  - Polywog 1907, 12296 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 13)
  - Polywog 1908, 12297 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 14)
  - Polywog 1909, 12298 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 15)
  - Polywog 1910, 12299 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 16)
  - Polywog 1911, 12300 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 17)
  - Polywog 1912, 12301 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 18)
  - Polywog 1913, 12302 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 19)
  - Polywog 1914, 12303 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 20)
  - Polywog 1915, 12304 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 21)
  - Polywog 1916, 12305 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 22)
  - Polywog 1917, 12306 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 23)
  - Polywog 1918, 12307 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 24)
  - Polywog 1920, 12308 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 25)
  - Polywog 1921, 12309 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 26)
  - Polywog 1922, 12310 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 27)
  - Polywog 1923, 12311 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 28)
  - Polywog 1924, 12312 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 29)
  - Polywog 1925, 12313 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 30)
  - Polywog 1926, 12314 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 31)
  - Polywog 1927, 12315 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 32)
  - Polywog 1928, 12316 (Item Shelf 37/4F, Item 33)
  - Polywog 1929, 12317 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 34)
  - Polywog 1930, 12318 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 35)
  - Polywog 1931, 12319 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 36)
  - Polywog 1932, 12320 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 37)
  - Polywog 1933, 12321 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 38)
  - Polywog 1934, 12322 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 39)
  - Polywog 1935, 12323 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 40)
  - Polywog 1936, 12324 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 41)
  - Polywog 1937, 12325 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 42)
  - Polywog 1938, 12326 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 43)
  - Polywog 1939, 12327 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 44)
  - Polywog 1940, 12328 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 45)
  - Polywog 1941, 12329 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 46)
  - Polywog 1942, 12330 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 47)
  - Polywog 1943, 12331 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 48)
  - Polywog 1945, 12332 (Item Shelf 37/5F, Item 49)
  - Polywog 1947, 12333 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 50)
  - Polywog 1948, 12334 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 51)
  - Polywog 1949, 12335 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 52)
  - Polywog 1950, 12336 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 53)
  - Polywog 1951, 12337 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 54)
  - Polywog 1952, 12338 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 55)
  - Polywog 1953, 12339 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 56)
  - Polywog 1954, 12340 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 57)
  - Polywog 1955, 12341 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 58)
  - Polywog 1956, 12342 (Item Shelf 37/6F, Item 59)
  - Polywog 1957, 12343 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 60)
  - Polywog 1958, 12344 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 61)
  - Polywog 1959, 12345 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 62)
  - Polywog 1960, 12346 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 63)
  - Polywog 1961, 12347 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 64)
  - Polywog 1962, 12348 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 65)
  - Polywog 1963, 12349 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 66)
  - Polywog 1964, 12350 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 67)
  - Polywog 1965, 12352 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 68)
  - Polywog 1966, 12353 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 69)
  - Polgwog 1967, 12354 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 70)
  - Polywog 1968, 12355 (Item Shelf 37/2E, Item 71)
  - Polywog 1969, 12356 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 72)
  - Polywog 1970, 12357 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 73)
  - Polywog 1971, 12358 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 74)
  - Polywog 1972, 12359 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 75)
  - Polywog 1973, 12360 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 76)
  - Polywog 1974, 12361 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 77)
  - Polywog 1975, 12362 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 78)
  - Polywog 1976, 12363 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 79)
  - Polywog 1977, 12364 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 80)
  - Polywog 1978, 12365 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 81)
  - Polywog 1979, 12366 (Item Shelf 37/3E, Item 82)
  - Polywog 1980, 12367 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 83)
  - Polywog 1981, 12368 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 84)
  - Polywog 1982, 12369 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 85)
  - Polywog 1983, 12370 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 86)
  - Polywog 1984, 12371 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 87)
  - Polywog 1985, 12372 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 88)
  - Polywog 1986, 12373 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 89)
  - Polywog 1987, 12374 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 90)
  - Polywog 1988, 12375 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 91)
  - Polywog 1989, 12376 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 92)
  - Polywog 1992, 12377 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 93)
  - Polywog 2001, 12378 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 94)
  - Polywog 2003, 12379 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 95)
  - Polywog 2005, 12380 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 96)
  - Polywog 2006, 12381 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 97)
  - Polywog 2008/2009, 12382 (Item Shelf 37/4E, Item 97)
  - Innovations 1986, 12383 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 98)
  - Innovations 1987, 12384 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 99)
  - Innovations 1988, 12385 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 100)
  - Innovations 1989, 12386 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 101)
  - Innovations 1990, 12387 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 102)
  - Innovations 1991, 12388 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 103)
  - Innovations 1992, 12389 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 104)
  - Innovations 1993, 12390 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 105)
  - Legacy 1994, 12391 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 106)
  - Legacy 1995, 12392 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 107)
  - Legacy 1996, 12393 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 108)
  - Legacy 1997, 12394 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 109)
  - Legacy 1999, 12395 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 110)
  - Legacy 2000, 12396 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 111)
  - Legacy 2001, 12397 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 112)
  - Legacy 2002, 12398 (Item Shelf 37/5E, Item 113)
- Series XVII: The Poly Prep and Polyglot, 11843
  Poly Prep and Polyglot are publications of Poly Prep Country Day School after Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute separated into two schools. Poly Prep moved to Bay Ridge and continued on as a prep school for boys, whereas the collegiate part of the institution became Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute, the precursor to today's NYU Polytechnic School of Engineering.
  - Poly Prep, Volume 1, 1899-1900; 12281 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 1)
  - Polyglot, 1901; 12282 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 2)
  - Polyglot, 1902; 12283 (Item Shelf 37/3F, Item 3)
- Series XVIII: The Polytechnic, 12275
  The Polytechnic was a periodical of campus news, letters, editorials, and fiction, 1890-1906.
  - The Polytechnic 1884, 12552 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic 1890, 12550 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic 1893, 12551 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic, March 1899 - November 1899, 12701 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic, December 1900, 12702 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic, January 1901 - April 1901, 12703 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic, January 1902 - May 1902, 12704 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic, February 1904 - December 1904, 12705 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic, February 1905 - May 1905, 12706 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic, January 1906, 12707 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Volume 1, 1890-1891; 12351 (Item Shelf 37/2F)
  - Volume 2, 1891-1892; 12399 (Item Shelf 37/2F)
  - Volume 3, 1892-1893; 12400 (Item Shelf 37/2F)
  - Volume 5, 1894-1895; 12401 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 4)
  - Volume 6, 1895-1896; 12402 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 5)
  - Volume 7, 1896-1897; 12403 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 6)
  - Volume 8, 1897-1898; 12404 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 7)
  - Volume 9, 1898-1899; 12405 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 8)
  - Volume 10, 1899-1900; 12406 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 9)
  - Volume 11, 1900-1901; 12407 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 10)
  - Volume 12, 1901-1902; 12408 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 11)
  - Volume 13, 1902-1903; 12409 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 12)
  - Volume 14, 1903-1904; 12410 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 13)
  - Volume 15, 1904-1905; 12411 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 14)
  - Volume 16, 1905-1906; 12412 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 15)
  - The Polytechnic 1899-1900, 12413 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 16)
  - The Polytechnic 1900-1901, 12414 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 17)
  - The Polytechnic 1901-1902, 12415 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 18)
  - The Polytechnic 1902-1903, 12416 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 19)
  - The Polytechnic 1903-1904, 12417 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 20)
  - The Polytechnic 1904-1905, 12418 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 21)
  - The Polytechnic Index, undated; 12419 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Volume 22)
- Series XIX: The Polytechnic Reporter, 11844
  The Polytechnic Reporter is the student newspaper of the Brooklyn campus (1914 - present).
  The following items represent bound volumes of the Polytechnic Reporter. Loose issues of the Polytechnic Reporter in box/folder arrangement are in The Polytechnic Reporter Collection, RG025.
- Series XX: Various small run publications, 11845
  - Administrative Bulletin, 1966; 12553 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Insights, 1977-1978; 12554 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Advising Newsletter, 1995; 12555 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Aero, 1967; 12556 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Alumni News, 1964-1966; 12557 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Annual Fund Newsletter, 1981-1982; 12558 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bits and Bytes-- Information Services Department, 2005; 12559 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Blue Jay-- Polytechnic Athletics Newsletter, 2005-2006; 12560 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Business Office Newsletter, 1980-1984; 12561 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Career Broadcaster, 2007; 12562 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Career Fair, 2003; 12563 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Career Notes, 1995-1997; 12564 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1977-1981; 12565 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Chemical Engineering Notes, 1998-1999; 12566 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Chemical Reactions, circa 1975; 12567 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Computer Newsletter, 1984; 12568 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - CSA Journal, 1980-1981; 12569 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - CUES Newsletter, 1971-1973; 12570 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Related Materials
    See RG.017, Guide to the Center for Urban Environmental Studies (CUES) Records, for additional CUES materials.
  - ECCP Newsletter, 1968; 12572 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - EE/CS News, 1983-1985; 12573 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - EE/EP, 1975; 12574 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Financial Services News, 2008-2009; 12575 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Impact, 1995; 12576 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Information Technology News, circa 2008; 12698 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Information Technology & Services Bulletin, 1993; 12577 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Infosys-- The Newsletter of Data Processing, 1987-1990; 12578 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Library News, 1991; 12579 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Library State of the Art, 1984; 12580 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Forum for Technology (LIFT), 1988-1990; 12581 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Long Island Review, 1994; 12582 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Metallury Alumni Newsletter, undated; 12583 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - MetroTech BID News, 2000-2002; 12584 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Microscope, 1984; 12585 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - News from the Departments, 1992-1994; 12586 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - News from Public Affairs, 1960-1968; 12587 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Placement Manual, 1972-1974; 12588 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Poly Flash, 1971; 12589 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Poly 100 Newsletter, 1994; 12699 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Polyphonics, 1995-1996; 12590 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - PolySWE Talk, 2007-2008; 12591 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Polytechnic Annual Fund Newsletter, 1982; 12592 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Polytechnic in Brief, 1967-1970; 12593 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Poly LI News, 1975-1976; 12594 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Polytechnic News Makers, 1984; 12595 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - PRD Reports, 1952-1955; 12596 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Renaissance Plaza Report, 1997; 12597 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Research News, 1987-1994; 12598 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Research Office Bulletin, 1964-1973; 12599 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - The Retorter, 1960; 12600 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers (SAE) Newsletter, 1976-1993; 12601 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Society for Human Resource Management (SHRM) Newsletter, 2001; 12602 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - SIAC News, 1992; 12603 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - The Spirit, 1980-1981; 12604 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Student Development, 2001-2003; 12605 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - The Technocrat, 1978; 12606 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - TTRC Newsletter, 1976; 12607 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Try Meditation, 2007; 12608 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Vision 2000, 1998; 12609 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - What's Up?, 1990; 12610 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - The Woodbird, 1957; 12611 (Box 11, Folder 70)